You know, I'm thinking about letting Emma have her first cookie.
我琢磨著該給艾瑪吃第一塊餅乾了
Her first cookie? She has cookies all the time.
第一塊？她常吃餅乾
I've never given her a cookie.
我沒餵過她餅乾
- Have you? - No.
-你給她了？ -沒有！
No. And for the record, I've also never given her frosting from a can.
另外，我也沒從罐子裡拿糖給她。
Hey, Rach, the adoption agency needs letters of recommendation..
瑞秋，領養中心要我們交一份推薦信。
and we wondered if you would write one for us?
你願意幫我們寫一封嗎？
- Of course. I would be honored. - Thank you.
-樂意效勞，我的榮幸 -謝謝
I think there's been an oversight.
怎麼不找我？
We would have asked you. We thought you wouldn't be interested.
喬伊，我們本想找你，但又覺得你可能沒興趣
It's just that we don't think of you as really being so much with the words.
我們覺得你可能不擅長跟文字打交道
Clearly, we were wrong.
看樣子我們錯了
I got a lot of nice stuff to say about you guys, okay?
對於你們二位，我有很多好話可寫
I know how much you want to have a baby..
而且我也非常清楚你們多想要個BB
and I would love to help you get one.
我很想幫你們
You know what? Then we want you to do it.
好吧，喬伊，你來寫
Thank you. All right. Let me see how I'm gonna start.
謝謝，我想想怎麼開頭。
"Dear Baby Adoption Decider People.."
親愛的嬰孩領養權決定人：
So excited about your letter.
迫不及待想看你寫的推薦信。
- Hey. - Hey, Phoebe.
-嘿！ -嘿！菲比！
- Wow, don't you look nice. - Yes, I do.
-你可真好看！ -沒錯，是很美
Today's Mike and my one-year anniversary.
今天麥克和我慶祝一週年。
What's it the anniversary of?
啥的週年？
Your first date, your first kiss, first time you had sex?
第一次親吻？第一次上床？
Yeah.
對。
So you must be going somewhere fancy to celebrate.
你們會去好地方隆重慶祝？
A Knicks game.
看尼克斯隊籃球比賽。
Aren't you a little overdressed?
你好像穿得過於隆重？
I've never had a one-year anniversary before..
我從未和哪個男人有過一週年。
so no matter where we go, I'm wearing something fancy..
所以不管去哪裡慶祝，我一定要盛裝打扮
I'm gonna put on my finest jewelry..
帶最好的珠寶
and we're gonna have sex in a public restroom.
還要在公共洗手間嘿咻。
You guys do that?
是嗎？
Chandler won't even have sex in our bathroom.
錢德連在我家洗手間嘿咻也不肯
That's where people make number two.
洗手間是尿尿的地方！
The One Where Rachel's Sister Babysits
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
So, you know, I have a little time if you want to..
我有點時間，你想不想
I'd love to, but I really have to grade these papers.
好想，但是要給卷子評分
Fine. It's fine.
好，那好吧
I'll just shower by myself.
那我就自己去洗澡
B. B. B. B. B.
「B」、"B"……
You gave a B to a Pottery Barn catalog.
你給陶器目錄也打了個"B"
Well, it had some good ideas. Take off your shirt.
他們表現尚可。脫衣服吧
- Damn it. - Rachel, open up! It's your sister!
- 該死！ -開門，瑞秋，你妹妹來了。
I have to talk to you.
我要談談
Hi, Amy.
嗨！艾米.
- You're not Rachel. - Still sharp as a tack.
-你才不是瑞秋 -牙尖嘴利
Charlie, this is Rachel's sister Amy. Amy, this is Charlie.
查理，這是瑞秋的妹妹艾米。艾米，這是查理。
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Hi, hi.
-很高興認識你 -嗨！
And you are?
你是？
Ross? I grew up on your block?
羅斯，以前跟你們住一個街區
We had Thanksgiving together last year?
去年我們一起吃感恩節大餐
I had a baby with your sister?
我和你姐生了個孩子
No. I..
不，我…
Did I buy a falafel from you yesterday?
昨天我從你那兒買了中東三明治？
Yes. Yes, you did.
沒錯
Hi, Rachel. Here's your sister Amy.
瑞秋，你妹妹艾米來了。
She thinks I need pec implants.
她說我應該胸肌整形
Amy? Hi.
艾米？嗨！
- You remember Joey. - Yeah. Hey, sure.
-記得喬伊嗎？ -當然
- The Days of our Lives guy. - That's right, yeah.
-《我們的日子》裡的演員 - 對！
You are not good.
你演得真濫
Always nice to meet a fan.
見到影迷總是高興
- So, now, what are you doing here? - Well, I have huge news.
-你來幹嘛？ -我有大新聞
- Hold on. Let me check on the baby. - This is important. Can't Ella wait?
-抱歉，先看看孩子 -我有很重要的事，愛拉不能等等？
Her name is Emma.
她名叫「艾瑪」
Why did you change it? Ella was so much prettier.
幹嘛改名呀？愛拉好聽多了！
What do I know? I just sell Middle Eastern food from a cart.
我哪曉得，我只是推著小車賣中東小吃的罷了
Hey, your English is getting better.
你英文有長進
- Oh, my God. - I know.
-天！ -對。
She may be the hottest girl I've ever hated.
她可能是我恨過的最辣的女孩
- What you working on? - Monica and Chandler's recommendation.
-你幹嘛？ -莫妮卡和錢德的推薦信
I want it to sound smart, but I don't know any big words or anything.
我想讓文字透著機靈勁 但深奧的詞我又不會
- Why don't you use your thesaurus? - What did I just say?
-那你試試"詞典" -我剛說了深奧的不會
Watch.
看著
Here, highlight the word you want to change, go under "tools"..
選中想改的詞
and the thesaurus generates.. Gives.
在工具條找到"詞典" 激活
Gives a whole list of choices.
「給出」候選詞語表。
You can pick the word that sounds smartest.
選一個更有學問的詞，就行了
My God, that's great. I'm smart.
太好了！我變機靈了！
No, no, I'm:
不，我變得
"Brainy, bright, clever." I love this thing!
「才華橫溢」、「聰明伶俐」 我愛這軟件
Look out, ladies! Joey Tribbiani's got the whole package!
各位，喬伊崔比阿尼 重裝上陣了！
God..
天！
so beautiful.
美極了！
I know, isn't she?
是啊，她好可愛
No, I was talking about your bedding.
不，我是說你的毯子
All right, what's your news, Amy?
艾米，啥新聞？
Well..
呃…
I'm getting married.
我要結婚了
Wow! Oh, my God!
天！
- To who? - This guy.
- 和誰結婚？ - 一個男人
He has a killer apartment.
他的房子太爽了
- And..? - And it's on Fifth.
-還有呢？ -在第五大道
And the elevator opens up right into the living room.
電梯開門就到起居室
- No, what's he like? - Oh, he's okay.
-他人如何？ -他還行
Do you remember my old boyfriend Mark?
還記得我以前的男朋友馬克嗎？
- Yeah. - It's his dad.
-記得 -我要嫁他爹
- Wow, so he's gotta be.. - Old? Yeah.
-那他可… - 太老了?對
But he travels a lot, so he's hardly ever there.
但他常常旅行，不怎麼呆在家
Sweetie, I gotta tell you, it sounds a little bit like..
你好像更喜歡他的房子
you like the apartment more than you like..
勝過...？
Myron.
馬瑞.
Yeah, I told you he was old.
說過他年紀大嘛
Sit down. Sit down.
坐下
Honey, you know..
寶貝，你知道嗎
I once also almost married somebody that I didn't love.
我也曾差一點嫁個我不愛的人
- Do you remember Barry? - Remember him?
-記得巴瑞嗎？ -記得？
God, we used to make out all the time after you went to sleep.
你睡了以後我們常一起鬼混
Sometimes just nodding is okay.
有時點頭回答就夠了
But anyway, listen.
不管怎麼樣，聽著
Not marrying Barry was the best decision that I ever, ever made.
不嫁巴瑞，是我一生最英明的決定
Honey, Amy, you deserve true love. Your soul mate is out there somewhere.
親愛的，你應該得到真愛 你的另一半就在某處
Someone that is your age, that is smart, that is fun..
一個同齡人，聰明而有趣，你也愛他
and that you care about.
在乎他
You're right.
沒錯。
- You're right. I'm gonna do it. - Okay.
-沒錯。就這麼干 - 好！
I'm gonna marry Myron and keep looking for Mr. Right.
我要嫁給馬瑞，再接著找我的另一半
Okay, let's keep talking.
接著說吧
Excuse me. Anniversary.
請讓讓，週年紀念
Sir, could you move your nachos? They're in my seat.
先生，請把玉米片挪挪 這是我的位子
It's my anniversary.
今天是我們的週年紀念
Here we are.
一年了
- I can't believe it's been a whole year. - I know.
-真不敢相信 -是啊
This has been the best year..
這是最好的一年
- This has been the best year of my life! - Me too!
-我一輩子最快樂的一年！ -同感！
I never thought I could love someone this much!
從不知道會如此愛一個人！
I feel the same way!
同感！
You're so generous and kind, and you're amazing in bed!
你慷慨又高尚，善良，在床上又好厲害！
It's our anniversary.
我們在慶祝週年
Knicks fans, please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
尼克斯的球迷們，請看亮分牌大屏幕這邊。
Someone has a special question to ask.
有人要問一個很特別的問題
How lame. It's so tacky and impersonal.
老套！俗氣！丟人現眼！
- Really? - It's the worst way to propose.
-啊？ -求婚下下策！
Excuse me.
失陪一下
I finished my recommendation. Here.
請看我寫的推薦信
And I think you'll be very, very happy.
你們一定要快樂得不得了
It's the longest I ever spent on a computer without looking at porn.
從來沒這麼久盯著電腦，居然沒去看色情站的
I don't understand.
看不懂
Some of the words a little too sophisticated for you?
有點太深奧？
It doesn't make any sense.
讀不順啊
Well, of course it does. It's smart. I used a thesaurus.
怎可能！我寫得很有學問的，我用了詞典啊
On every word?
每個詞都用？
Yep.
沒錯
All right, what was this sentence originally?
這句話原本是啥意思？
"They are warm, nice people with big hearts."
他們是熱心的好人
And that became, "They are humid, prepossessing Homo sapiens..
結果變成：他們是潮濕的 給人好感的智人人類
with full-sized aortic pumps."
具有標準尺寸的心臟大動脈
Yeah. Yeah. And hey, I really mean it, dude.
我真心這麼想
All right, Joey, I don't think we can use this.
喬伊，恐怕我們不能用這封信
- Why not? - Well, because you signed it:
-為什麼？ -因為你的簽名是：
"Baby Kangaroo Tribbiani."
袋鼠寶寶：小崔 （有一個卡通袋鼠形象叫喬伊）
Why don't you stop worrying about sounding smart and just be yourself.
算了，你還是不要假裝有學問 就用你的本色來寫怎麼樣？
You don't need a thesaurus. Just write from here.
你不必用詞典，要用「心」寫
Your full-sized aortic pump.
讓它發自你的標準尺寸的心臟大動脈？
- Amy. Hi. - I took your advice.
- 艾米！嗨！ -我聽了你的話
- I left Myron. - Good for you!
-我跟馬瑞分手了。 -太好了
I know. I'm Erin Brockovich.
是啊，簡直像電影女主角！
Yes, you are.
對。
- I'm so proud of you. - Thank you.
-以你為榮 - 謝謝
So can I stay with you?
我能住你這裡嗎？
But Erin Brockovich had her own house.
電影女主角不是住她自己家嗎？
Look who's back.
看誰又來啦
Why do you have bags? Why does she have bags?
你怎麼帶行李？ 她為什麼帶行李？
I'm staying with you guys.
我要和你們住一塊了
- What? - We're gonna be roomies!
- 什麼？ -我們是同居室友了！
Come on.
來。
- You slept out here? - Yeah.
-你睡在外面？ - 是啊！
Amy kept kicking me in her sleep, yelling, "Myron, get off!"
她夢中把我踢出來 還叫囂什麼：馬瑞，滾出去！
But we're getting rid of her, right? Please tell me we're getting rid of her?
我們會把她趕走對吧？ 答應我，趕走她
- Joey, I can't do that. - Oh, come on.
-我下不了手，喬伊 -噢, 不會吧.
Last night I was finishing off a pizza, and she said:
昨晚我剛吃完一半披薩，她就說
"A moment on the lips, forever on the hips."
嘴上爽一把，屁股胖一生
I don't need that kind of talk in my house!
在我家不許說這種話！
Joey, look, I know that she's difficult..
喬伊，我知道她難相處
but I think it's really good that she's here.
但她來這裡也不錯
Because we'll appreciate it more when she's gone?
這樣她滾蛋後我們才能更歡喜？
No, it's just.. Look, when I first moved to this city, I was a lot like her.
我剛搬來還不是一樣
I was spoiled, self-centered. And you guys really took care of me.
被慣壞，自我中心 你們幾個卻照顧我
Yeah. Monica made us.
莫妮卡強迫我們來著
Well, whatever. I really appreciate it..
不管怎樣我都很感激
because I don't think I would be the person I am today..
如果沒有你們
if it wasn't for you guys.
也就沒有現在的我
So I want to help Amy the way you guys helped me.
我想幫幫艾米，就像你們幫我那樣
And I know it's gonna take patience, but that's okay.
我知道這需要極大的耐性，我可以
- Good morning. - Yeah.
-早 -早
That's what I'm wearing today. That's why I hung it on the door.
艾米，那是我今天要穿的衣服 所以我才掛在門上。
Oh, sweetie, you can't pull this off.
寶貝，你總不能給我扒下來
You know what? I was thinking that maybe now would be a good time..
你知道嗎，現在我們也許應當坐下來
for us to sit down and, you know, talk about your future.
好好談談你的將來
Oh, I can't, honey. I'm gonna go get my eyebrows shaped.
我沒空，我要去修眉
I am not happy.
這樣的眉毛像哭喪著臉
Sure you want to eat that?
你真要吃剩下的一半？
I'm curvy and I like it!
我就是想增加曲線美，我喜歡！
- Hi. - Hi.
-嗨！ -嗨！
I just had the worst anniversary ever.
最爛的週年慶！
I doubt that. Tell her about us last year.
才不是呢 莫妮卡，給她講講我們去年怎麼過的週年
Well, I bought Chandler a $500 watch, and he wrote me a rap song.
我給錢德買了500圓一隻的表。 而他，給我寫了首饒舌歌。
- Seriously? - Word.
-真的？ -是..
Mine was worse than that.
我的比你還遜
- Well, what happened? - We were at the game.
-怎麼啦？ -球賽時
This guy proposed to his girlfriend on the big screen thing.
有人在大屏幕上求婚
- That is so tacky. - Well, that's what I said.
-老套！ -我也是那麼說
But it turns out Mike was planning to propose to me that same way last night.
結果呢，原來麥克昨晚上就想用 這種方式向我求婚！
Oh, my God. Mike was gonna propose?
天，麥克要求婚？
- That's huge. - Do you want to marry him?
-大事件！ -你想嫁他嗎？
Yeah, I really do. Yes.
當然想啦！
But after I dumped on the way he was gonna do it..
結果我那句話把他堵回去了
I don't think he'll ever ask again. I said no in Barbados, and now this?
我想他一輩子都不會求婚了。 在巴貝多我拒絕過他一次了，現在又
She's right. If I were a guy and..
沒錯。如果我是男人
Did I just say, "If I were a guy"?
我剛才是不是說： 如果我是男人？
You don't need him to propose to you. Maybe you could propose to him.
別等他求婚了，主動出擊吧
Oh, I don't know. I don't know. Isn't that a little desperate?
哦，不知道，我又不是想嫁想瘋了
I proposed to Chandler.
我向錢德求的婚
All right, moving on.
好吧，就算是
I don't think it was desperate. It was amazing.
我不覺得你想嫁想瘋了，我覺得你很棒
Thank you.
謝謝。
- Well, do you think I should propose? - I think it could be kind of great.
-你們都認為我該求婚？ -那一定很棒
Absolutely. You'll love the feeling. There's nothing like it.
當然！世上再沒有比求婚更美妙的感覺了！
Okay. Okay. So how should I do it?
好，就這麼干
How about at a game on the big screen?
在球賽的大屏幕上告白
How about at a Foot Locker?
更老套的求婚方式如何？
What? What, he obviously thinks that's a nice way to be proposed to.
他既然選擇過大屏幕求婚，可見他能接受這種方式
- Plus, he'd never suspect it. - Yeah, that does make sense.
-而且他也不會起疑心 -有理
- Okay, now, would you two like that? - Sounds good to me.
-你們會喜歡嗎？ -我喜歡
But what would a guy think?
不過男性會怎麼想？
- Nana's on the phone. - Wow.
-奶奶電話 - 哇！
That's interesting, since she died seven years ago.
有趣，她七年前就死了
She did?
是嗎？
Who got her condo in Boca?
那她在博卡的房子歸誰了？
Hello?
喂
It's our nanny.
是我們的保姆
Hi.
喂
Oh, God, I hope you feel better. Okay. Bye.
是嗎，希望你早點康復。再見
That's Molly. She's sick.
是莫麗，她病了
- Can you watch Emma today? - I can't. I have back-to-back classes.
-今天你看孩子可以嗎 - 不行， 我要連堂上課
Did Molly say what she had? Because my throat's been hurting.
莫麗說她生什麼病？我的喉嚨也不舒服
Menstrual cramps.
痛經
I don't think that's what this is.
我可能不是這毛病
- Can any of you watch Emma? - No, I'm sorry, sweetie.
-你們幫忙看著艾瑪成嗎？ -抱歉，親愛的
No, I've got work, and then I'm proposing.
我要上班，還要求婚
Great. Shoot. What am I gonna do?
那怎麼辦
Well, I could do it.
我可以幫手
- Well, actually.. - Can I talk to you for a second?
-好 -談談？
I do not want her babysitting our child.
我不贊成。
- Why not? - For one thing, she keeps calling her Ella.
-為啥？ -首先，她老是把我們的孩子喊成「愛拉」
- Ella's a nice name. - Fine, we'll call the next one Ella.
-這名字也不錯嘛 -好，下一胎叫"愛拉"
- The next one? - Okay.
-下一胎？ - 好
I don't want her watching our baby.
我不贊成她幫我們看孩子
Ross, I am trying to help her become a better person.
我只是想改造她
This is a huge breakthrough for her.
這是個好機會
She just offered to do something for another human being.
可以教她為別人做點事
You know, I don't know.
我不懂
Ross, I'm telling you..
羅斯，我是說
she's giving up getting her eyebrows shaped to do this, all right?
她寧願犧牲修眉的時間看孩子
Do you understand how important that is in our world?
這件事對我們意義重大！
Listen, I couldn't help but overhear, because I was trying to.
我不小心聽到你們的談話。 因為我想聽
Listen, let me do this. I really want to help you guys out.
就讓我帶孩子吧，我真心想幫你們
And plus, Rachel's been so wonderful to me.
而且，瑞秋對我太好了
- Absolutely. - Oh, great!
-好！ -太好了!
So how much does it pay?
付多少工錢？
How's the second draft of the letter coming?
喬伊，二稿如何？
Great. I'm finished. In fact, I just dropped it off at the agency.
殺青了，剛剛交了
- You dropped it off? - Yeah.
-交了？ - 是啊。
Can we read it? Can you print out another copy?
我們能讀讀嗎？再打印一份給我們？
No can do, amigo.
哎呀，恐怕不行，
No, I didn't use the computer. It felt more personal to handwrite it.
沒用電腦，手寫的，顯得更親切
- You handwrote it? - Yeah, and don't worry.
-還手寫？ -別擔心
I didn't try to sound smart at all.
我根本沒有裝老練
See you later.
再見
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That letter is gonna go in our file.
天，信快寄到了。
We're never gonna get a kid.
我們沒指望了
We're gonna be one of those old couples..
我們會孤獨終老
that collects orchids or has a lot of birds.
養花弄鳥
It's okay. You know what?
別急
I will just call the agency and tell them to throw out the letter.
我打電話給領養中心 請他們扔掉那封信
Okay, good.
好。
Hello, this is Chandler Bing.
喂，我是錢德賓
Someone just dropped off a handwritten recommendation letter and..
有人手寫了一封推薦信
Okay.
對，對，好
Thank you. Goodbye.
謝謝，再見
We're screwed, aren't we?
我們完蛋了，知道嗎
You know what? Just tell me on the way to the bird store.
先去買鳥，路上說給我聽
- They loved it. - What?
-他們喜歡那封信 -什麼？
They thought it was very smart of us to have a child write the letter.
他們說我們很聰明，叫個小孩寫推薦信
They thought Joey was a child?
他們以為喬伊是小孩？
She guessed 8,9, based on his drawings.
他們看了他的畫，以為他只八九歲
- Hi. - Hey, what'd you guys do today?
- 嗨！ -嗨！你們今天幹嘛了？
Ella wanted to go out, so we went shopping and got some sushi.
愛拉想上街，所以我們去購物 還買了壽司
- That sounds like fun. - Yeah, not really.
-有趣 -也不是啦
Babies are dull.
BB很無趣
- Hey. Hi, how's my girl? - I'm fine.
-我家妹妹怎樣了？ -我很好
And I got you a present for letting me stay with you.
我給你買了禮物，謝謝你留我住
- Ready? - Yeah.
-準備好了？ - 嗯！
You pierced her ears?
你給她穿了耳洞？
Doesn't it make her nose look smaller?
她的鼻子看來小點了嗎？
You pierced her ears?
你給她穿了耳洞？
How could you do this without telling me?
竟然不徵求我同意？
If I had told you, then it wouldn't have been a surprise, now would it?
我若先告訴你，就不是驚喜了
I think she looks cute.
我想她看來很可愛
But I am wrong.
但我錯了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Here comes Ross. He's gonna flip out.
天，羅斯會發飆的
Why, did something happen to his falafel cart?
中東女孩不能穿耳洞嗎？
- Hey, guys. - Ross!
- 嗨，各位！. - 羅斯！
Hi, Emma. Why is she wearing her hat so low?
嗨，艾瑪。 她的帽子幹嘛壓這麼低？
- She can barely see. - I don't really want her to see.
-她都看不見了 -人家不想她看見嘛
Why not?
為啥？
Because there are so many terrible sights in this world.
世界太可怕
Like war. Or that thing in Joey's refrigerator. Remember?
有戰爭，還有喬伊冰箱裡那玩意兒
It was in a milk carton, but it looked like meat?
一隻牛奶盒，但看來像塊肉
Come here. Come here.
快來，快來
There she is. Hi.
看她多乖
- What? - Nothing.
-怎麼啦？ -沒啥
Hi.
嗨！
What..?
什麼?
- Please tell me those are clip-ons! - Oh, they're real.
-那是夾上去的？ -是戴上的
Did she do this to her?
是她幹的？
I told you we shouldn't have left Emma with her!
我早說過不能把艾瑪交到她手上！
I know, I know. And you were right, Ross.
我知道了！你說得對
Okay? You are so irresponsible! I am never letting you babysit again!
你太不負責！ 絕不再讓你看孩子！
You know what? This kid needs me, okay?
你們知道嗎？ 她需要我！
- She needs to have a cool, fun aunt. - I'm a cool, fun aunt.
-她需要一個又酷又有趣的阿姨！ -我就是！
Okay.
好吧
Hey! Monica can be cool and fun at organized indoor projects.
莫妮卡就是又酷又有趣，而且有條有理！
All I wanted to do was help you try to figure out what to do with your life.
我只不過想幫你想清楚你將來想幹什麼！
This is how you repay me?
結果呢，你還是小孩子？
I don't need you to help me. I already know what I'm gonna do with my life.
誰稀罕你幫忙。我自己想好了
- Oh, yeah? Since when? - Since today.
-是嗎？幾時想好的？ -今天
I am going to be a baby stylist.
我要當BB時尚專家！
- What? - That's not a thing!
-啊？ -有這職業嗎？
Well, it should be.
應該有！
I'm gonna help babies learn how to accessorize..
我要教BB如何穿戴
what colors to wear, what clothes are slimming.
選衣裳的顏色，什麼衣服較瘦身
- Babies don't care if they're slim! - Enter Amy.
- BB才不想苗條呢！ -如何像艾米一樣美！
- Amy, I.. I just.. I just wanna.. - What? What are you gonna do?
- 艾米, 我要… -你想怎樣？
No more falafel for you!
罰你永世沒有三明治吃！
Great game, huh?
比賽很精彩
- Why do you keep looking at the screen? - I'm not. I'm praying.
-你怎麼老瞄大屏幕？ -沒，我在禱告
Please let the Knicks win.
請讓尼克斯隊贏吧
Thank you, Thor.
謝謝！托爾(北歐神話中的雷神)
- Where are you going? - I'm going to the bathroom.
-你上哪兒？ -噓噓去
- Well, I think you should wait. - Why?
-等一會 -為啥？
Well, if you don't hold it in, you don't get all the nutrients.
如果不憋一會，你就無法攝取所有養分
Knicks fans, please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
尼克斯球迷，請注意積分牌大屏幕
Someone has a special question to ask.
有人要問特別的問題
Mike Hannigan, will you marry me?
麥克漢那根，娶我好嗎？
Get a load of this. She's proposing to him!
看啊，她向他求婚！
Guess we know who wears the pants in that family.
到底誰更有種？
Well, that's not very enlightened.
不要誤導觀眾！
Boo us? Boo you!
不許噓我們！
Odin will smite you!
你們去死！
Hello? Yeah, this is Joey Tribbiani.
喂？我就是喬伊崔比阿尼
Oh, hi.
哦，嗨！
Well, I'm glad you liked my letter.
真高興你喜歡我的信
No, my mommy and daddy aren't home right now.
我爸媽不在家
Okay, bye-bye.
再見
She was nice.
她真慈祥
Joey, get Amy's bags. She is moving out.
喬伊，把艾米的箱子拿出來，她要搬走了
- You're kicking me out? - You put holes in my baby's ears.
-你把妹妹踢出家門？ -你給我的BB穿耳洞！
At least now people will know she's a girl!
不然大家怎麼知道她是女孩？
I can't believe I ever even tried to help you.
不敢相信，我竟然想過要幫你！
- You are so beyond help! - You know what?
-你不可救藥！ - 你知道嗎？
Ever since I got here, you have been nothing but negative.
這次見面你在否定我的一切！
- Excuse me? - You didn't want me..
-啊？ -你不准我…
to marry the old guy with the great apartment.
不准我嫁有豪宅的老頭
Then I tried to help your daughter de-emphasize her flaws..
我想幫你把你女兒的鼻子變小點
and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
結果吃力不討好？
- Joey, where are those bags? - She has a lot of crap!
-喬伊，行李怎麼還沒搬出來？ -她的破玩意太多了
You know? When I moved in here, I thought, "This will be so great.
我剛搬來時，還想著太好了
Just us sisters back together again like when we were kids."
憧憬著姐妹團聚 像童年那樣
Except without that stupid Jill.
而且沒有該死的吉爾搗亂
Who has gotten fat, by the way.
她變肥了
Seriously?
真的？
Mom said she gained, like,15 pounds.
媽說吉爾肥了15磅
- Hips or thighs? - Ass and face.
-屁股和大腿長肉了？ -屁股和臉
Oh, my God! I thought she was on Atkins.
天啊，她不是節食嗎？
She was. Carbs found her.
本來是，後來被男人甩了
See? This is what I wanted.
看，這才像姐妹
Two sisters talking about real stuff.
真心交談
Oh, I can give you that.
哦，我可以這樣
- You can? - Yeah.
- 你可以？ - 是的。
I kept trying to make you a better person, but you're..
我老想改造你。實際上
You're already a pretty perfect version of what you are.
你本來就接近完美了
Thank you.
謝謝你
You gotta admit, Emma does look cute.
必須承認，艾瑪真可愛
- Did you just say, "Emma"? - Oh, I'm sorry. Ella.
-你剛說「艾瑪」？ -對不起， 愛拉
Sis, you wanna go bring Jill some pasta?
姐, 你要給吉爾帶意大利面?
Come on, Amy. Now, that's just wrong.
艾米. 那些是錯的.
Her true weakness was garlic bread.
她真的怕的是大蒜奶油麵包片.
That woman didn't know what she was talking about, Mike.
賽場裡那傢伙真是亂講
Obviously, you have balls.
你當然有種
- Please, let's forget the whole thing. - I would love it.
-忘了算了 -你能忘最好
- Consider it forgotten. - Thank you.
- 已經忘了 - 謝謝
But just so you know..
不過你知道...
However and whenever you decide to propose, I promise I'll say yes.
不管你何時、以何方式求婚 我保證答應
Whether, you know, it's at a basketball game..
不管是籃球賽
or in skywriting..
還是寫在空中
or, you know, like some lame guy in a cheesy movie..
或是像有部濫電影裡
who hides it in the cake.
把求婚信藏在蛋糕裡
It's in the cake, isn't it?
是蛋糕對吧？
Where else would lame Mr. No Balls hide it?
沒種的男人還會有什麼好點子嗎
What's the matter with me? Why do I keep ruining this?
我是怎麼了？怎麼老提這個！
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - No, it's my fault.
-對不起嘛 -是我錯
I keep trying to propose in these stupid ways..
我老用愚蠢的方式求婚
and I just wanna tell you I love you, and I wanna spend my life with you..
我只是想告訴你 我愛你，我想和你度過餘生
- I'm gonna do this now. - Oh, my God.
-我現在求婚 -天啊
- Phoebe, I.. - Wait. Oh, wait.
-菲比 -暫停
Oh, no.
暫停
Okay.
好了。
Ready? Okay.
可以了？
Phoebe, I love you.
菲比，我愛你。
There's no one else in the world I would ask to marry me three times.
這個世界只有你我會三次求婚
But I want to take care of you..
我想照顧你
have babies with you..
和你生兒育女
and grow old with you.
一起變老
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
菲比布費，你願意嫁我嗎
Yes.
我願意！
- I love you. - I love you more.
-我愛你 -我愛你更多
Not possible.
不可能
She's gonna be Mrs. No Balls!
她是「沒種夫人」了
So how's the baby-styling business going?
「BB時尚專家」好當嗎？
Not that great.
行情不大好
It's almost as if people don't want to hear that their babies are ugly.
好像大家都不愛聽見他們的BB丑
That's shocking.
吃驚
There's Ross. Hey, Ross.
那不是羅斯嗎？羅斯！！！
Hello, Ross?
你好，羅斯！
He's rude.
真沒教養